<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Muriden - Xenotype Project</name>
	<author>DanZinagri</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>DanZinagri.Muriden</packageId>
    <modVersion>0.4.1</modVersion>
	<description>
	Muriden - From Muris (Latin for Mouse).
	
	I like the ratkin mods and the themes it adds, but i've been a bit burned by how hefty HAR and the various race mods can get on a heavily modded setup. While i've seen a attempt or two at a general biotech conversion they felt a little base-level and many didn't recapture theire smaller size. Thus i wanted to make a mod to not only add in a similar type, but also tie it in with the big and small framework. As such i hope to make a ground-up rework of the "ratkin" theme and even add my own spin to it.
	
	What is added:
	Muriden - Effectively the baseliner of this ratkin-esk race.
	Sciurus - A fast but fragile squirrel subtype (name continuiing with the latin theme).
	Dirtmole - Patched to be a subtype of Muriden, gaining more of the traits of the Muriden while still retaining the benefits of the dirtmole. (didn't change the name to try and limit compatability issues).
	A Medieval-Tier faction called the Muriden Kingdom (currently able to spawn Muriden and Dirtmoles)
	
	Future Plans:
	New equipment
	Hostile faction
	New Xenotypes
	Equipment for higher tech levels
	VFE Medieval and Medieval Overhaul integration
	special Muriden Warcaskets
	
	I'm learning modding this stuff as I go so for now this mod will be mostly XML changes, but maybe someday i'll actually read up on the C# modding side if i run into something i can't achieve with XML changes.
	
	I will continue to try and make improvements on the textures as well.
	</description>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>oskarpotocki.vanillafactionsexpanded.core</li>
		<li>redmattis.betterprerequisites</li>
		<li>redmattis.bigsmall.core</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>